# Jamie Lynn

Self-Taught Javascript/Python Web Developer

513 Grace Ln
Coppell, Tx 75019
(972) 440-9156
toby2494@hotmail.com
seolynn.com
Jamielynn.dev
https://github.com/feeby2494

Self-taught python/javascript developer that has been building python apps and hosting on Digital Oceans for the past 4 years, while I worked on hardware repair as my day job. I don't consider myself entry level anymore, but because I never worked on a development team I do consider myself as a junior. With that said, I would quickly become mid level with the right opportunity and constant feedback. I'm not a sales person nor am I dishonest, so it's hard for me to market myself in this day and age where dishonesty is required to get your first job. I don't play that game. I want experience in a team to become a senior developer, then go off and start my own company. The end goal is to build more confidence, better understanding, and empower myself to live by my own rules.

### **PROJECTS**

# Django App for Web Project submission

For my freelance business offering Data Analysis and Web Development. Possible to send orders in with multiple projects, two step registration, and user login/logout features.

Links: Github

## Django Vue Blog

A Simple Django Restframework / Vue Blog with images, iframes, and many elements per post possible.

Links: Github-backend Github-frontend

### Mobile Repair Mail-in Service Version 2

Planned to replace Seolynn.com with Django/Vue app for faster development and more optimized/stable code. Less custom code.

Links: Github-backend Github-frontend

### **seolynn.com**— Mobile Repair Mail-in Service

Site I use for online repair business. Possible to submit device for repair, users can login to see their devices along with progress. Admin can view all devices and change status of devices. Flask with React used.

Links: Live Site Github-FullStack

# **chromebooks.v3.jamielynn.dev**— Chromebook and Macbook parts Reference and Inventory Management Application

One of my first Flask/React apps I made to tackle the issue my repair team

#### **SKILLS**

React.js, Flask, Django, Vue.js, Wordpress, PHP, Nginx, Linux, Bash, Digital Oceans, Rest API, Node

#### **LANGUAGES**

English (Native), Korean (Intermediate Beginner), Japanese (Beginner) was facing at AGi Repair. I needed a centralized app to look up part numbers for chromebooks and macbooks. Later added inventory that corresponds to physical location codes on shelves. Dealt with Json Web Tokens for user authentication.

Links: Github, Live Site

# **jamielynn.dev**— Personal Site, Language Learning Tools, and Portfolio

My personal Flask/React site. Have not worked on it for a while. Have two apps to help me learn Korean and Japanese.

Links: <u>Github</u>, <u>Live Site (Home)</u>, <u>Live Site (Vocab Quiz)</u>, <u>Live Site (Points app)</u>

#### **EDUCATION**

## **University of North Texas,** Denton, Tx — Bachelors or Arts

Aug 2011 - Aug 2015

I actually don't remember the dates very well. I wanted to take Electrical Engineering, but my math skills were really bad. I then tried Information Technology, but at that time I didn't enjoy programming. I choose International Studies, because I thought I would be okay at teaching English abroad and I like learning about new cultures. I'm good at history and cultural studies, so it was something I excelled at. I now regret this decision for two reasons: first, I don't need a degree to study and appreciate other cultures; second, computer or Electrical theory would have given me the basis I lack today. I burned my time.

# **Coursera,** Online — Google Certificates

Jan 2020 - Oct 2022

- Google IT Authentication Certificate ( Certificate Link )
- Google IT Help Desk Certificate ( Certificate Link )
- Meta Backend Developer Certificate ( 4 out of 9 completed )

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **AGi Repair Tx,** Carrollton, Tx — Chromebook Tech (was Facility Manager)

MONTH 2016 - PRESENT

I worked myself up from iPad tech to computer repair lead, then to assistant manager, then to facility manager, then everything fell apart. My issue with management is I'm too nice to my employees and don't like putting my fist down. Granted the situation I was dealing with was something beyond my abilities. I don't want to be a manager until I know how to handle people with more assertiveness. I also created the chromebook/macbook inventory application when I worked here. I was not a part of the official development team, but because I made this app for a business issue and my office used it, I consider this professional

experience. I'm still appalled that my company didn't choose me as a developer, but it may have come down to lack of PHP experience.

# **Ministry of Education, Science and Technology**, Jeonju-shi, Jeollabuk-do, Korea(the one everyone loves) — *TALK Scholar*

MONTH 2013 - MONTH 2015

Talk program (Teach and Learn in Korea) is the program I was in. Talk scholar is an English Teaching Assistant and Afterschool Teacher. I used Korean as much as I could, but hit some limits in my ability with the language. I plan to build up my grammar and vocabulary, then take the TOPIK certifications. I loved and still love Korea and the Korean language, but teaching English wasn't for me. I found out I enjoyed learning/teaching about technical things like Linux and web development around this time.